Guide to the New York State College of Home Economics records, 1875-1979
Cornell University, New York State College of Home Economics records,
- Series XIII: Scrapbooks and Miscellany
  - Scrapbooks
    - Two small scrapbooks of Martha Van Rensselaer-related clippings (Box 48)
    - Three large scrapbooks of Home Economics clippings (Box 48)
    - Scrapbooks Disassembled Scrapbook of "Let's Make a Dress" Radio Show - 3 folders (Box 48)
    - Scrapbook: The Cayuga Indian Feast (Box 49)
    - Scrapbook: Martha Van Rensselaer's Mother (Box 49)
    - Scrapbook: Wartime Conservation (Box 49)
    - Letter Book: Martha Van Rensselaer, 1901-1905 (Box 49)
    - Letter Book: Martha Van Rensselaer, 1902-1905 (Box 49)